Aether is a unified toolkit for authorized security testing of modern identity fabrics.

Usage:
  aether [flags]
  aether [command]

Available Commands:
  ad          Active Directory operations (Kerberos, LDAP, AD CS)
  audit       Tamper-evident audit trail (signed hash chain)
  cap         Conditional Access policy operations
  completion  Generate the autocompletion script for the specified shell
  connect     Connect to the teamserver as an authenticated operator
  dashboard   Token-authenticated web dashboard: graph view + activity stream
  doctor      Check host environment health
  exec        Cloud command execution (governed: audit + rollback recorded)
  export      Export evidence, reports, and graph topologies
  graph       Cross-provider identity graph
  help        Help about any command
  ldap        LDAP enumeration and ACL analysis
  pivot       Cross-boundary pivoting operations
  plan        RL planner: train, export episodes, generate adaptive plans
  plugins     Plugin registry: search and install community plugins
  providers   Third-party provider plugins (okta, gitlab, kubernetes)
  prt         Primary Refresh Token operations
  relay       Authentication relay operations
  replay      Replay past operations from a runbook (dry-run by default)
  rollback    Revert engagement changes (deterministic cleanup)
  run         Execute the kill chain inside a workspace
  serve       Start the mTLS teamserver (cert-bound operators, capability authz, spine dispatch)
  simulate    Emulate SOC telemetry and log signals (detection engineering)
  token       Token Protection & channel binding operations
  tunnel      Single proxy reachability probe via an external proxy (HTTP/SOCKS5) — not a tunnel
  validate    Attack path validation and OPSEC scoring
  watch       Continuously monitor the environment for new attack paths
  workspace   Engagement workspace management
  ztna        ZTNA broker detection & broker-routed execution

Flags:
      --config string      Config file path
  -h, --help               help for aether
      --log-level string   Log level (debug, info, warn, error) (default "info")
  -v, --version            version for aether

Use "aether [command] --help" for more information about a command.
===
